

# **Professional Skills**

Basic Design Knowledge Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop Canva

Basic HTML & CSS Knowledge

#### Others

Microsoft Office Social Media Management Content Creation Project Management

# **Education** History

# University at Buffalo (SIMGE)

Bachelor of Arts (Communication)

- Attended from Aug 2019 - Aug 2021 (Expected GPA: 3.5)
- Dean's List Spring 2021

# Singapore Polytechnic Diploma in Media and Communication

- Attended from 2016 to 2019 (GPA: 3.24)
- Edusave Good Progress Award 2019

# **Work Experience**

## Project Management Intern TBWA\ Singapore Sept. 2018 to Apr. 2019

- Serviced the SIA account
- Managed ATL & BTL assets
- Work closely with Brand Management and Creatives to ensure flow of day-to-day work.
- Managed timelines on various projects

# Retail Associate (Part Time) Pull & Bear Apr. 2019 to Aug 2019 Nov 2019 to Jan 2020

- Assist on floor and fitting room duties
- Assist during visual merchandising
- Stock take

# Hotel Receptionist Hotel YAN

Dec 2017 - 02/2018

- Front desk duties, liaising housekeeping
- Keeping check of customer accounts during check-in and out

# **Summary**

A forward-looking individual, I strongly believe in taking initiative in my work. My passion in the marketing and advertising industry has led me to continue pursuing Communication studies in university. Having experienced life in an agency during my internship, I'm accustomed to working with tight deadlines and thrive under pressure.

### Certifications

Google Ads Search Certification

#### **Contact**

+65 81634066 joeykong99@gmail.com

## References

Luke Tan (Singapore Polytechnic Lecturer) luke\_tan@sp.edu.sg

# **Notable Works**

# View at jieyiii.wixsite.com/hello

### **IMC Work**

# Sustenance of Samsung S8 & S8+ (2017)

- Aim of brief: Create buzz-worthy campaign to promote S8 & S8+.
- Team was shortlisted to present campaign to Starcom Mediavest.
- Role: Troubleshooter, Budgeting, Media Planning and Copywriter for social media platforms.

# "Don't Be Afraid to Be Polite" with Singapore Kindness Movement (2016)

- Aim of brief: Create a campaign to cultivate residents of HDBs to take better care of their neighborhoods.
- Team was shortlisted to present to Singapore Kindness Movement and I was selected for the client presentation.

# "Don't Hide Just Seek" with Singapore Kindness Movement(2017-2018)

- Aim of brief: Execute an event to cultivate neighbourliness in secondary school students
- Role: Social Media Manager for all social media platforms. Includes ad purchasing and monitoring on various social media accounts and copywriting.
- @donthidejustseek (Instagram Account)

## Social Media Work

# SkillsFuture MOE Instagram Takeover (2018)

- Aim of brief: Create social media campaign to create hype for SkillsFuture 2018
- Role: Social Media Manager. Took over @moesingapore's Instagram account for event coverage. In-Charge of facilitating actual day event coverage video and activities.
- @moesingapore (Instagram Account)

## **Production Work**

# RF360 Healthy Living & Workplace Safety (2017-2018)

- Aim of brief: Produce and film corporate videos for RF360.
- Role: Team Lead & Producer.
   In-charge of leading my team to plan and shoot the videos. I was also the main liaison with the client.

# Radio and TV Production and Management Live Show (2017)

- Aim of brief: Produce and film live game show for polytechnic year 2 production project.
- Role: Producer and Team Lead. In-charge of overall artistic direction and content for both live and recorded content. Planning of timelines and led meetings.